Howard, ugh,
my father was a police officer.
(Bernadette:)We never knew
from one night to the next...
...if he was gonna come home alive.
It was horrible.
(Bernadette:)And I don't want to live
that way with you.
Well, hey...
(Howard:)...my father abandoned me
and my mother when I was 11.
(Howard:)We never saw him again.
Oh, boo hoo, you're not going to space.
- Pretty cool about Howard, huh?
- Don't talk to me...
(Sheldon:)...as if nothing's happened between us.
And yes, it sure is, buddy.
(Leonard:)Will you stop
with the Schrödinger stuff?
Would you prefer an application
of Heisenberg's uncertainty principle?
(Sheldon:)In which I could either
know where you are...
(Sheldon:)...or whether I like you, but not both?
(Leonard:)You never stop talking, do you?
What difference does it make
if Leonard goes to wil wheaton's party?